[Music]
we are here today in the insurance asia
magazine headquarters in singapore to
celebrate the winners of the most
prestigious awards in the insurance
industry in the asia pacific region the
insurance asia awards 2021
prudential has won the international
life insurer of the year award and the
new insurance product of the year award
for vietnam and congratulations on your
two award wins
thank you simon
um bond and i are very proud to
represent financial vietnam today to
receive
not just one but two awards from
insurance asia this year we we have a
very ambitious um goal objective that we
don't we not just wanted to be
the leader in terms of market share but
also we wanted to be the role model
of the entire life industry
in vietnam
for the core strategy of customer
centricity and sustainable growth we
wanted to do the right thing the best
thing for our people
and provide the right solution for
customers at the right time
[Music]
well you know when we introduced a new
product
we also introduced some new very new
concept the market for example we
thought that the hair body parts would
be very okay to the vietnamese client
because when they jump to the hell
journey they need to have something to
support them in a long journey
on very soft terms we sold more than 100
000 who received
and up to now more than 6 000 customers
they have benefit they can pay good new
claim and get the support from the
producer
[Music]
you